

Kostas Tsalikides 28-02-1990



Thessaloniki, Greece



0030 698 7040 946



kostas.tsalikides@gmail.com



Portfolio

### **EXPERIENCE**

1/2017 - present Freelancer

Macbook Air, Thessaloniki, Greece

Development of commercial websites, web applications, mobile

applications and web games.

9/2016 - 1/2017 Front-End Developer

Circles Ltd, Limassol, Cyprus

I've been part of a team for the implementation of the user interface of a WiFi prototype. I have worked with Atlassian Software in an agile

environment developing new features.

# **EDUCATION**

9/2014 - 12/2015 **Master** (M.Sc.)

Innovation in Technology and Entrepreneurship

Eastern Macedonia and Thrace Institute of Technology, Kavala

2/2008 - 9/2012 **Bachelor** (B.Sc.)

Computer Science and Telecommunications (Grade 7,54)

Technological Educational Institute of Epirus

## **PROGRAMMING SKILLS**

- JavaScript
  - o jQuery, AngularJS, ReactJS, VueJS, PixiJS
- HTML, CSS
  - o Bootstrap, Bulma
- PHP
  - CodeIgniter, Laravel

#### **SKILLS**

Foreign Languages: Level 1 Certificate in English (ESOL), Grade C

Certificate of Competency in English (University of Michigan)

## **LEISURE**

- Watch Video Gamers streamings
- Playing LOL or something else online
- Playing Chess

#### **ABOUT**

Hello, I'm Kostas Tsalikides, an experienced Web Developer with more than six years of hands-on experience in Web Technologies. I have worked on several projects with HTML, JavaScript, and PHP. Currently, I'm trying to follow up with the latest Front-end technologies such as Angular, VueJS, ReactJS and PixiJS. With my current experience, love for coding and passion for delivering clean and reusable code, I would be a great asset for your company.